

# **ANH NGUYEN NGOC**

# MARKETING EXECUTIVE

## CAREER OBJECTIVE

Become a multitask Marketing Executive staff. Learn more experiences and challange myself in an entirely new working environment. That helps me to get more useful customer service experiences, as well as improving market research skills. Through that, I can enhance market analysis skills and marketing strategy planning for many different fields.

# **EDUCATION HIGHLIGHT**

RMIT University | July 2016 - Dec 2019 Bachelor of business Minor: Marketing

Email: nguyenngocanh171196@gmail.com ann.marketing96@gmail.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **AMWAY**

Product Marketing Specialist| June 2020- Present

Admin & Logistic support:

- To handle admin jobs related to product SKU acquirement (IR/PR/PO), product ordering, product launch, promotion, activation, events...
- To manage promotional stock and keep track of the product//brand sales performance
- To liaise with purchasing team and vendors To coordinate with training team to translate and prepare for training events

# Brand & Product Management Support:

- To collect and update competitive information
- To work on Overlabels of the products, product visa, product claims
- To communicate with related department regarding the product/brand activities
- To monitor , analyze, & evaluate product performance & Distributors/ Consumers' feedbacks To coordinate with advertising & media agencies to prepare for advertising plan

#### **LOTTE E-COMMERCE**

Marketing Campaign| Nov 2019 - May 2020

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Assist to control goods in and out with MD
- Mange stock, keep track of products on sites
- Market research to collect and update competitive information
- Run Marketing Automation Campaign System
- Attend Marketing Skill Course in the Company

# LT PACIFIC INVESTMENTS

Sale admin intern | Feb 2019 - June 2019

- Support marketing event team and sale team
- Mange FB fanpage
- Advertise on media publications such as: banner, posters, leaflets...
- Make reports of the end of months.

Achievements and skills gained:

- Knowledge of Melbourne real estate area
- Improve English Communication Skill.

### **ACTIVITIES HIGHLIGHTS**

# **RMIT SAT**

Member of RMIT Student Ambassador Team | July 2016 - Dec 2019

- Organize monthly events, network with students
- Run many different RMIT events such as Campus tour, Career Expose, Graduation Event
- Share student's life experiences to all freshers

## PROJECT WITH MEGA GS CINEMA

Change beverage consumer behavior at Mega GS cinema

- Support Mega GS to bring C2 herbal tea products to the customers, specifically is moviegoers
- Analysis
- Research buyer behavior
- Plan strategy and evaluate

# SKILLS

Language: Advanced English

Computer: Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Another: Teamwork skills, Problem Solving skills, Critical

thinking skills